<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Another RecyclerView</string>
    <string name="book_list_title">Book List</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="book_preview">Book preview</string>
    <string name="book_details">Book Details</string>
    <string name="book_details_sample">One of the legendary media titles of all-time, Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep? has a lot to do with androids and a little bit to do with electric sheep. It hints at one of the more pressing questions about robotics, though, which is the capacity for robots to think – Philip Dick was considering the issue in 1968. The book was the basis for the movie Blade Runner.If you were to see this Celeste Ng novel in a bookstore, you would probably think, “That’s going to be a really sad story about someone dying.” And you would be right. The title grips a reader because they want to know what wasn’t told and why it wasn’t told. Everything I Never Told You is so much more than a sob story, though, and that’s why it won countless awards back in 2014.If you were to see this Celeste Ng novel in a bookstore, you would probably think, “That’s going to be a really sad story about someone dying.” And you would be right. The title grips a reader because they want to know what wasn’t told and why it wasn’t told. Everything I Never Told You is so much more than a sob story, though, and that’s why it won countless awards back in 2014.If you were to see this Celeste Ng novel in a bookstore, you would probably think, “That’s going to be a really sad story about someone dying.” And you would be right. The title grips a reader because they want to know what wasn’t told and why it wasn’t told. Everything I Never Told You is so much more than a sob story, though, and that’s why it won countless awards back in 2014.If you were to see this Celeste Ng novel in a bookstore, you would probably think, “That’s going to be a really sad story about someone dying.” And you would be right. The title grips a reader because they want to know what wasn’t told and why it wasn’t told. Everything I Never Told You is so much more than a sob story, though, and that’s why it won countless awards back in 2014.</string>
    <string name="author_title_sample">Love in the Time of Cholera by Gabriel García Márquez</string>
    <string name="rating_count_sample">21 Reviews</string>
    <string name="language_sample">FR</string>
    <string name="price_sample">15 EUR</string>
    <string name="published_date_and_publisher_sample">Lafond on 12/04/2015</string>
    <string name="isbn_sample">1542484569842</string>

    <array name="book_images">
        <item>@drawable/adult_blur_books</item>
        <item>@drawable/alphabet_blur_books</item>
        <item>@drawable/animal_bookcase_books</item>
        <item>@drawable/antique_black_and_white_books</item>
        <item>@drawable/apple_blackboard_books</item>
        <item>@drawable/background_books_business</item>
        <item>@drawable/blur_books_close_up</item>
        <item>@drawable/book_book_pages_chapter</item>
        <item>@drawable/book_pages_books_close_up</item>
        <item>@drawable/book_stack_books_classic</item>

    </array>

    <string-array name="books_titles">
        <item>Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep? by Philip K. Dick</item>
        <item>Everything I Never Told You by Celeste Ng</item>
        <item>Is Everyone Hanging Out Without Me? (and Other Concerns) by Mindy Kaling</item>
        <item>The Electric Kool-Aid Acid Test by Tom Wolfe</item>
        <item>Are You There, Vodka? It’s Me, Chelsea by Chelsea Handler</item>
        <item>The Devil Wears Prada by Lauren Weisberger</item>
        <item>The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-Time by Mark Haddon</item>
        <item>How to Win Friends and Influence People by Dale Carnegie</item>
        <item>Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs by Judi Barrett</item>
        <item>Love in the Time of Cholera by Gabriel García Márquez</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="books_descriptions">
        <item>One of the legendary media titles of all-time, Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep? has a lot to do with androids and a little bit to do with electric sheep. It hints at one of the more pressing questions about robotics, though, which is the capacity for robots to think – Philip Dick was considering the issue in 1968. The book was the basis for the movie Blade Runner.One of the legendary media titles of all-time, Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep? has a lot to do with androids and a little bit to do with electric sheep. It hints at one of the more pressing questions about robotics, though, which is the capacity for robots to think – Philip Dick was considering the issue in 1968. The book was the basis for the movie Blade Runner.One of the legendary media titles of all-time, Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep? has a lot to do with androids and a little bit to do with electric sheep. It hints at one of the more pressing questions about robotics, though, which is the capacity for robots to think – Philip Dick was considering the issue in 1968. The book was the basis for the movie Blade Runner.One of the legendary media titles of all-time, Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep? has a lot to do with androids and a little bit to do with electric sheep. It hints at one of the more pressing questions about robotics, though, which is the capacity for robots to think – Philip Dick was considering the issue in 1968. The book was the basis for the movie Blade Runner.One of the legendary media titles of all-time, Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep? has a lot to do with androids and a little bit to do with electric sheep. It hints at one of the more pressing questions about robotics, though, which is the capacity for robots to think – Philip Dick was considering the issue in 1968. The book was the basis for the movie Blade Runner.</item>
        <item>If you were to see this Celeste Ng novel in a bookstore, you would probably think, “That’s going to be a really sad story about someone dying.” And you would be right. The title grips a reader because they want to know what wasn’t told and why it wasn’t told. Everything I Never Told You is so much more than a sob story, though, and that’s why it won countless awards back in 2014.</item>
        <item>Mindy Kaling gets right to the heart of the issue in this comedic autobiography. Let’s be real: we all ask this question when we’re laying in bed on a Friday night, curled up with a book. At least if we’re reading Is Everyone Hanging Out Without Me? we’ll have Mindy by our side! </item>
        <item>The Electric Kool-Aid Acid Test screams cool, since nothing is cooler than Kool-Aid…and electricity. And LSD, especially in the 1960s. Tom Wolfe’s nonfiction story details the touring life and LSD use of a band. That’s a pretty cool story to tell.</item>
        <item>Instead of looking for God, Chelsea Handler is looking for a drink in Are You There, Vodka? It’s Me, Chelsea. It’s funny and blatant, just like the comedian. The best-selling autobiography of essays helped to launch Handler into even greater fame.</item>
        <item>Before it was a feature film (and soon-to-be Broadway musical), The Devil Wears Prada was a best-selling book. Lauren Weisberger’s title sticks so well because of the imagery it invokes, with an illusion of a fiery being wearing Prada heels. We’ve probably all met someone like this, too… </item>
        <item>The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-Time is now a successful stage adaptation, but the title lacks some originality; it’s actually a Sherlock Holmes quote from an Sir Arthur Conan Doyle short story. Mark Haddon applies it perfectly, however, to the story about a savant who is just a bit different than everyone else.</item>
        <item>One of the best selling self-help books of all-time, How to Win Friends and Influence People immediately gets to the point. Dale Carnegie wanted people to be influenced by his book about influencing people and a title about finding success was the perfect way to get people’s attention.</item>
        <item>The classic children’s book uses a spectacular image to grab people’s attention: Could you imagine looking up in the sky and seeing meatballs beginning to rain down? That’s the colorful image the equally colorful book creates with its title. Judi Barrett’s then-husband, Ron Barrett, helped the title come to life with some stunning illustrations.</item>
        <item>Love in the Time of Cholera is one of the most respected books of all-time. It helps to have a title that raises the stakes before a reader even opens the novel. Gabriel Garcia Marquez notes “time” in his title, but the story has a tragic, timeless quality about it. You already know that a story of love during an epidemic that killed thousands will be heart-wrenching. </item>

    </string-array>
</resources>
